timely.is 2011-10-06

# Flowtown Privacy Policy

Flowtown, Inc. (“Flowtown“) knows that you care about how your personal information is used and shared, and we take your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy. By visiting the www.Flowtown.com website and domain name, or otherwise accessing any other linked pages, features, content, or services offered from time to time by Flowtown in connection therewith (collectively, the “Website“), you acknowledge that you accept the practices and policies outlined in this Privacy Policy.

## WHAT DOES THIS PRIVACY POLICY COVER?

This Privacy Policy covers Flowtown’s treatment of personally identifiable information ("Personal Information") that Flowtown gathers when you access the Website and when you use Flowtown’s services. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Flowtown does not own or control, or to individuals that Flowtown does not employ or manage.

## WHAT PERSONAL INFORMATION DOES FLOWTOWN COLLECT?

The information we gather from customers enables us to personalize and improve our services. We collect the following types of information from our customers:

### Personal Information You Provide to Us:

We may receive and store any information you enter on our website or provide to us in any other way. For example, when you register for the Website we ask for information such as your name and email address. Flowtown uses collected information for the following general purposes: products and services provision, billing, identification and authentication, services improvement, contact, and research. In addition, we collect the e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail, aggregate information on what pages consumers access or visit, and information volunteered by the consumer (such as survey information and/or site registrations).

### Contact Lists

To fully utilize the Website, you must import email contact lists (e.g. for your potential customers, etc). Your contact lists are stored on a secure Flowtown server. We do not steal your list, contact your list, market to your list, sell your list, or share it with any other party, unless required to by law or regulation. Your contact list is kept confidential. Only authorized personnel have access (for customer service and abuse-monitoring purposes) to view system accounts and campaigns. We do not hold your lists hostage. They are your property.

### Cookies

A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier, that is sent to your browser from a web site’s computers and stored on your computer’s hard drive. Cookies are required to use Website. We use cookies to record current session information, but do not use permanent cookies. You are required to log-in to the Website after a certain period of time has elapsed to protect you against others accidentally accessing your account contents.

## DATA STORAGE

We use third party vendors and hosting partners to provide the necessary hardware, software, networking, storage, and related technology required to run the Website. Although we own the code, databases, and all rights to the Website, you retain all rights to your data.

## WILL FLOWTOWN SHARE ANY OF THE PERSONAL INFORMATION IT RECEIVES?

Personal Information about our customers is an integral part of our business. We neither rent nor sell your Personal Information to anyone. We share your Personal Information only as described below.

_Affiliated Businesses We Do Not Control:_ We anticipate that we may become affiliated with a variety of businesses and work closely with them. In certain situations, these businesses may sell items to you through the Website. In other situations, Flowtown may provide services jointly with affiliated businesses. You can easily recognize when an affiliated business is associated with your transaction, and we will share your Personal Information that is related to such transactions with that affiliated business. 

_Agents:_ We employ other companies and people to perform tasks on our behalf and need to share your information with them to provide products or services to you. Unless we tell you differently, Flowtown’s agents do not have any right to use Personal Information we share with them beyond what is necessary to assist us. You hereby consent to our sharing of Personal Information for the above purposes.

_Promotional Offers:_ We may send offers to you on behalf of other businesses. However, when we do so, we do not give the other business your name and address. If you do not wish to receive these offers, please send an email with your request to opt-out@flowtown.com

_Business Transfers:_ In some cases, we may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of transactions, customer information is typically one of the business assets that are transferred. Moreover, if Flowtown, or substantially all of its assets were acquired, or in the unlikely event that Flowtown goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, customer information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of Flowtown may continue to use your Personal Information as set forth in this policy.

_Protection of Flowtown and Others:_ We may release Personal Information when we believe in good faith that release is necessary to comply with the law; enforce or apply our conditions of use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of Flowtown, our employees, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

_With Your Consent:_ Except as set forth above, you will be notified when your Personal Information may be shared with third parties, and will be able to prevent the sharing of this information.

## CONDITIONS OF USE

If you decide to visit the Flowtown websites, your visit and any possible dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of California state law.

## THIRD PARTY WEBSITES; APPLICATIONS

Flowtown services may permit you to link to other websites on the Internet, and other websites may contain links to the Websites. These other websites are not under Flowtown control, and such links do not constitute an endorsement by Flowtown of those other websites or the services offered through them. The privacy and security practices of websites linked to or from the Flowtown websites are not covered by this Privacy Policy, and Flowtown is not responsible for the privacy or security practices or the content of such websites.

## IS PERSONAL INFORMATION ABOUT ME SECURE?

Your Flowtown account Personal Information is protected by a password for your privacy and security. You need to ensure that there is no unauthorized access to your account and Personal Information by selecting and protecting your password appropriately and limiting access to your computer and browser by signing off after you have finished accessing your account.

Flowtown endeavors to protect user information to ensure that user account information is kept private, however, Flowtown cannot guarantee the security of user account information. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors, may compromise the security of user information at any time.

## WHAT CHOICES DO I HAVE?

You may request deletion of your Flowtown account by sending an e-mail to help@flowtown.com. Please note that some information may remain in our records after deletion of your account.

## SIMPLE AND QUICK OPT-OUT

You can opt out of the Flowtown database at any time. Simply [click here](http://optout.flowtown.com/) and you will be permanently removed from our database.

## CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

Flowtown may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is used. If we make changes in the way we use Personal Information, we will notify you by posting an announcement on our Website or sending you an email. Users are bound by any changes to the Privacy Policy when he or she uses the Website after such changes have been first posted.

## QUESTIONS OR CONCERNS

If you have any questions or concerns regarding privacy on our Website, please send us a detailed message at help@flowtown.com. We will make every effort to resolve your concerns.

Effective Date: January 1, 2010

Flowtown Inc.  
2601 Mission St. Suite 602  
San Francisco, CA 94110
